(Sheldon(outside):)Knock, knock,
knock, Penny?
(Sheldon(outside):)Knock, knock, knock, Penny?
Knock, knock, knock, Penny?
(Penny:)What's this?
(Sheldon:)Leonard told me what happened,
(Sheldon:)so I took it upon myself
to make you a hot beverage.
(Penny:)Oh. That's so sweet of you.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. I know.
(Sheldon:)Turns out, being sweet
(Sheldon:)isn't enough
to keep a girl these days.
(Sheldon:)I blame Madonna.
(Penny:)I'm sorry to hear
about you and Amy.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm sorry
about Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Thought I raised him
better than that.
(Penny:)You know, it's bad enough
what happened,
(Penny:)but then he tried to hide
the fact that he sees her
(Penny:)all the time
at the university.
(Sheldon:)He does? Who is it?
(scoffs) Some girl named Mandy.
(Sheldon:)Mandy Chao?
Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Oh, you don't need
to worry about her.
(Sheldon:)She's brilliant and attractive.
(Sheldon:)She can do way better
than Leonard.